The radiance of the night shines through my window
but the path to immortality is long.
The Eight Views and Nine-Bend Streams are desolate.
Living beings question the miseries of the world over a jar of wine.
Forget about Nirvana and rebirth,
I will break through the waves with my own flesh and blood.
The heavens are vast, so what if I was born mediocre ?
I stare at the Dao in my moments of madness
as the storm rages just below.
I've been thinking about life and death in my dreams.
I've unsheathed my sword to ask the immortals
why the world is a-changing.
Heaven and earth reveals its poignant truths.
Swallow the Four Seas and the Eight Wastelands,
experience all the vicissitudes of life in an instant.
I will defy the light in the sky
to continue to write a new chapter for all things in the three realms of existence.
Just a thought separates mortal from immortal.
Transform your insignificant body into light.
The hardships of the journey
will temper this young man's heart.
If I become a Renegade Immortal, will I hesitate to fight the heavens ?
Renegade Immortal\NSubtitles by Bonobosubs\Nhttps://discord.gg/Ceckd4pdVA
Greetings, Immortal.
In which direction is the country of Zhao ?
Lord Immortal,
Zhao is in this direction.
But there is a dangerous place on the way
called the Black Swamp.
That place is cursed.
Neither Immortals nor mortals can go through it.
I suggest you avoi...
Yeah, sure.
This place is dangerous ?
It's just a normal swamp.
What the hell is this !?
Too weak...
Is this where Teng One is hidden ?
Why is there no sect
guarding the first Spirit Vein ?
Fellow cultivator doesn't know,
this vein is in a bottomless swamp.
Teng One cultivates there alone.
For 400 years, the Core Family Members rotated a lot
but Teng One's name
has never changed owners.
With his strength,
there is no need to guard this vein.
Are you the person Teng Huayuan
spoke of ?
Don't complicate things.
Come out !
Lord Immortal, calm your anger.
Master is invincible !
Be it Teng One or Teng One-Hundred,
they cannot match you !
It failed ?
Teng One\NTeng Family Core Member\NPeak Late stage Nascent Soul
He...he...
can resist Master !?
Teng Huayuan really raised 8 morrons.
He really woke me up
to deal with a mere Early stage Nascent Soul brat ?
He's fast.
His cultivation is deep...
winning will be hard.
Dragon Restriction,
activate !
He is not afraid of the Ji Realm
and his body is strong.
But he can be injured by the Restriction Flag.
10 000 Swords Restriction,
activate !
Is this it ?
You're too weak.
His body is on the verge of collapse
but he neither dodges nor retreats.
Something's wrong...
Slash !
So you can destroy by body...
you deserve praise.
Still alive ?
Not bad.
Ancestor,
we should ask other clans
to assist Master Teng One
and ensure his victory.
Teng One is my disciple, the kind of genius
that is born only once per thousand years
He is only a step away from Soul Formation.
Because of his special Spirit Root,
he was selected by the Envoy for a large scale experiment.
The 9 Spirit Veins of Zhao
all feed the first Spirit Vein.
In the Nascent Soul Realm,
Teng One is unmatched.
As long as Wang Lin isn't Soul Formation,
he will
die today.
He died and already revived ?
The Ji Realm is useless against him ?
Master,
let's run away !
No,
Teng One must have a weakness.
Spirit Roots ?
Not only did they take the spiritual energy from the mortal's Spirit Roots,
but the Spirit Roots themselves are missing.
The millions of Spirit Roots...
Where are they ?
The whole Black Swamp
is made of Spirit Roots !
Not just the swamp...
Teng One's body
is also made of Spirit Roots.
He completely refined his body
to merge it with this place.
He relies on the Spirit Roots in the swamp to revive.
As long as there are Spirit Roots, he cannot die.
My only shot is to sever his connection with this place,
and kill him then.
Little brat,
you've been fooling around for a long time already,
you can be proud of yourself.
Is this...
a restriction !?
When did you make it ?
You are the one who is fooling around.
Underworld Sealing Restriction,
activate !
Such a large restriction
to cut me off from all the Spirit Roots at once...
I wanted to use the restriction to delay you
but freezing the Spirit Roots
is even better.
What a domineering strength...
Good, good !
I haven't enjoyed a good fight like this for years.
Little brat,
this is the first time in 400 years
that I had to use this trick !
This power...
feels really familiar...
Mere tricks !
Is this...
Ancient God Blood !?
Turns out such an artifact exists.
It seems
he can only attack with it.
Futile !
No matter how powerful your artifact is,
it will only delay your death !
Not necessarily.
Explode !
Using a drop of Ancient God Blood
to imitate the original ?
You will never grasp its essence.
Little brat,
let go !
Before you die,
I will let you see
the power of a real Ancient God.
One drop is enough
to summon the Ancient God's Demon Guardian.
Attack !
To think that I
would actually...
Interesting...
Very interesting...
Reporting to Ancestor,
the restriction around the city cannot be breached.
Junior requests Ancestors and the Nascent Soul Elders to act now.
Forgive me Ancestor !
Forgive me !
We Juniors are unable to handle this task.
This will...
Ancestor ?
Teng One...
Master Teng One, he...
he...he...
Issue the order.
All the disciples of the Teng Family
must immediately return to Teng Family City.
Summon the remaining Core Members
to follow me to activate the defense formation.
Wang Lin...
I've had my share of wounds,
now I want to fight back.
Is my destiny a wall of restrictions
that's blocking all my hopes
for life ?
My flesh and blood witnessed the past,
my adversity pushed me to brave the waves.
How do you navigate through the years passing by ?
Nirvana and rebirth are no longer
out of reach.
Immortals
are obsessed with delusions of grandeur.
Renegades
seek to crush the impermanence of the heavens.
Don't tell me that I overestimate myself
and that the path to revenge leads to hell
because I don't see the harm in that.
My new body opens its eyes
and awakens from its dream.
I have overcome many trials
to get this body back.
No matter how many endless dark nights go by,
I can still see.
By sticking to this thought, I will get it done
by my own hands.
Returning to my body opened my eyes,
I need to continue my Immortal journey.
With a flick of a finger,
only my indomitable heart remains.
Life and death trials temper me, I am not afraid of losing my soul.
Even if there are countless tribulations and hardships.
Overcome this fate, smash through the obstacles,
like the descent of a god.